Hello everyone and welcome to this week's episode of This Just In, English Pod's news and features show.
So here we're talking about the news at English Pod and some lessons coming up.
So my name is Catherine and I'm joined here in the studio by Bill.
Hello, I'm Bill.
So there's not many of us in the studio this week as you've noticed the trend.
A lot of people are on the holiday, so we're sorry for that.
Marco is probably getting a tan somewhere exotic.
That sounds like something Marco would do.
Yeah, jerk.
That jerk, yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
All right, well, we do have some lessons coming out.
They're really great lessons.
Less holiday focused, thank goodness.
Everything's kind of behind us now.
It is a new year.
The first one is about the farm.
So we've got a lesson called farm animals coming up.
We're going down to the farm.
That's right.
Do you know the song?
Going down to the farm?
No, the other song.
Farmer John?
No.
Oh, yeah.
Wait for it.
Bingo?
Oh, McDonald.
Oh, yeah.
All right, well, e-i-e-o, that's the joke.
All right.
Our lesson on Monday is an elementary level lesson,
so you'll be learning all about farm animals
and things that go on in the countryside.
So it's a very fun lesson for those of you city dwellers
who are not too familiar with that.
On Wednesday, though, we have an upper intermediate level lesson.
This is more of a business focus.
Right.
There's going to be somebody writing a business plan, I believe.
That's correct.
And so this person might not have much of a business background,
it seems, because he has no idea what he's doing.
Well, that doesn't really preclude his chances for success.
There are a lot of businesses out there that weren't started
by strictly businessmen.
True, true.
I think the key, though, is to have a goal.
This guy doesn't even seem to know what he wants to do,
so that's an important centerpiece.
He's pretty clueless, it sounds like.
So that's Wednesday's lesson, and on Friday,
we have a lesson about going on a diet.
That's an intermediate level lesson.
An appropriate time of year for a lesson like this.
Exactly.
Well, we often say that at the new year,
people want to make resolutions.
It's a good time to start a diet.
So this is a very timely lesson about trying to get into
smaller clothes and how to go on a diet
without starving yourself.
That's the key, isn't it?
Yeah.
Not starving is generally a life goal people have.
Well, unfortunately, I think a lot of people are misinformed
and they believe that's basically what dieting is, right?
I mean, when I recorded earlier,
I was talking to another colleague and she said,
well, that's the best method, right?
It's just starving yourself for like a week or something.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm not going to ask who it was.
Well, yeah.
No, definitely the focus in this lesson
is on eating healthfully and not just cutting out all food.
That's how I would do it if I was going to go on a diet.
Well, that's our final lesson for the week.
We do have an episode of Director's Cut coming out on Tuesday.
So for those of you who don't know,
Director's Cut is our movie show
where we just sit around and talk about movies.
Yeah, that's what a movie show is.
So I heard you're a big fan of this one.
This one is one of my absolute favorites.
No, I'm just kidding.
Are you into why hard?
I've never seen any of these movies.
The Twilight movies.
Right.
So it's a trilogy.
I know nothing about them.
There's three or four books and they're all being made into movies.
Quadrilogy.
Well, the first one was called Twilight
and it came out a couple of years ago.
And it was very popular, so popular.
The people who are fans have a special name.
They're called TwiHards.
TwiHards.
Yeah, like Die Hard.
Oh, I get it.
It's funny.
And this movie is called New Moon.
And so this is the sequel to the first one
and it was pretty popular in the States.
Yeah, well, you know, actually,
where this whole series takes place
is actually fairly close to my home.
Oh, in the Pacific Northwest.
In the Pacific Northwest,
in a little town named Forks, I believe.
I don't know if you've read it,
or any of the stories or anything,
so you don't know the background.
So we went out there.
This is kind of out in the sticks,
out in the country.
You might see some farm animals out there.
That's where a lesson from Monday
would come in very handy.
So we were out there fishing, actually.
And we stopped to get bait at a bait shop
and it was like,
Twilight tours available.
I thought you were going to say
you got attacked by a wolverine.
Why?
Are there wolverines in the story?
Apparently, I haven't seen it,
but that's the big...
Your background knowledge is a little spotty.
You know some various things.
I sit next to Liliana
and she is obsessed.
She's a TwiHard.
She is totally a TwiHard.
I'm not going to say it.
All right.
Okay.
Well, I've heard it's a beautiful part of the world
and a lot of the movie takes place there
or some of it in Italy, I guess.
And I have to go see it.
But that's going to be the topic
for this week's Director's Cut.
So check that one out
if you're at all interested.
Or if you're a teenage girl.
Yeah, or boy.
Or boy.
Sorry.
Don't want to exclude anybody.
All right.
So that aside though,
we do have a lot of stuff going on here
because it's a new decade, obviously.
The subscription price change has happened.
So we hope that you got your purchase on time.
If not, you can still make a purchase.
And English pot is always a good gift for a friend
if you're late on your holiday shopping.
Indeed.
But the big question is,
this is a new decade.
What the heck do we call it?
Is it the tens?
Is it the tweens?
The tweens?
The teens?
I mean, it's just the tens.
Well, I guess maybe we would have to break it down
and for the first three years call it the tweens
and call it the teens for the next seven after.
All right.
So teens like 19, 18, 13, these are teens,
like people you say he's a teenager.
So years you can say it's the teens.
But until then we just call it the tens.
Tweens.
In between.
But you know,
I actually don't really see a need for this
as we were talking about earlier.
I didn't even know there was a name for this decade
or the decade previous.
So the last decade.
From 2000 to 2009, what did we call that?
Nobody called that anything.
I called it the aughts,
but people made fun of me.
So I just stopped calling it anything
because there was never a decision about what to call it.
But as we've heard, apparently,
the second was called the naughties
or the aughts or the aughties.
The aughts.
Aughts.
Aughts means zeros.
What's the difference between the aughts and aughts?
Where you come from.
If you have a pack the car in the garage.
So, yeah, so it depends where you live.
Yeah, apparently.
So, okay,
if you have any confusion, don't ask us.
We don't know.
But it is a new decade.
Enjoy it.
Go on a diet if you're feeling overweight.
And if not, just enjoy the...
Go to a farm, visit farm animals.
Yeah, and watch New Moon.
Let us know how it is.
Make a business.
Maybe you could make a business involving farm animals.
These are all good things.
Take a trip.
Start a business.
Go on a diet.
Great things with a new year.
Go watch New Moon.
New Moon.
Alright, that's it for us today here at EnglishPod.
Hope you've enjoyed this and have a great week.
Bye, everyone.
Bye-bye.
EnglishPod.com